
Available Templates

  Hello World (Go)
      ID: hello-world-go  |  Language: go
      A minimal cron-triggered workflow to get started from scratch

  Hello World (TypeScript)
      ID: hello-world-ts  |  Language: typescript
      A minimal cron-triggered workflow to get started from scratch

  Block Trigger (Go)
      ID: block-trigger-go  |  Language: go
      Process new blocks and transactions using block-triggered webhooks with watched address matching.

  Block Trigger (TypeScript)
      ID: block-trigger-ts  |  Language: typescript
      Process new blocks and transactions using block-triggered webhooks with watched address matching.

  Indexer Data Fetch (Go)
      ID: indexer-fetch-go  |  Language: go
      Pull data from The Graph indexer on a cron schedule using GraphQL queries.

  Indexer Data Fetch (TypeScript)
      ID: indexer-fetch-ts  |  Language: typescript
      Pull data from The Graph indexer on a cron schedule using GraphQL queries.

  KV Store (Go)
      ID: kv-store-go  |  Language: go
      Read, increment, and write a counter in AWS S3 using SigV4-signed HTTP requests.

  KV Store (TypeScript)
      ID: kv-store-ts  |  Language: typescript
      Read, increment, and write a counter in AWS S3 using SigV4-signed HTTP requests.

  Read Data Feeds (Go)
      ID: read-data-feeds-go  |  Language: go
      Read Chainlink Data Feeds on-chain, decode price values, and return results on a cron schedule.

  Read Data Feeds (TypeScript)
      ID: read-data-feeds-ts  |  Language: typescript
      Read Chainlink Data Feeds on-chain, decode price values, and return results on a cron schedule.

  Read MVR Data Feeds (Go)
      ID: read-mvr-data-feeds-go  |  Language: go
      Read Multiple Variable Response (MVR) data feeds via BundleAggregatorProxy on a cron schedule.

  Read MVR Data Feeds (TypeScript)
      ID: read-mvr-data-feeds-ts  |  Language: typescript
      Read Multiple Variable Response (MVR) data feeds via BundleAggregatorProxy on a cron schedule.

  Bring Your Own Data (Go)
      ID: bring-your-own-data-go  |  Language: go
      Bring your own off-chain data on-chain with Proof of Reserve (PoR) and NAV publishing.

  Bring Your Own Data (TypeScript)
      ID: bring-your-own-data-ts  |  Language: typescript
      Bring your own off-chain data on-chain with Proof of Reserve (PoR) and NAV publishing.

  Custom Data Feed (Go)
      ID: cre-custom-data-feed-go  |  Language: go
      Fetch custom off-chain data and push it on-chain using cron and log triggers.

  Custom Data Feed (TypeScript)
      ID: cre-custom-data-feed-ts  |  Language: typescript
      Fetch custom off-chain data and push it on-chain using cron and log triggers.

  Multi-Chain Token Manager (Go)
      ID: multi-chain-token-manager-go  |  Language: go
      Maximize lending yields via automated cross-chain rebalancing using CRE with CCIP.

  Multi-Chain Token Manager (TypeScript)
      ID: multi-chain-token-manager-ts  |  Language: typescript
      Maximize lending yields via automated cross-chain rebalancing using CRE with CCIP.

  Install a template with:
  cre init --template=<id>

